[
  {
    "no": "01",
    "question": "What is Prisma?",
    "options": [
      "A cloud computing platform",
      "A database management system",
      "A frontend JavaScript framework",
      "A design tool"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "A database management system"
  },
  {
    "no": "02",
    "question": "Which programming language is primarily used with Prisma?",
    "options": ["Java", "Python", "JavaScript/TypeScript", "Ruby"],
    "correctAnswer": "JavaScript/TypeScript"
  },
  {
    "no": "03",
    "question": "What role does Prisma Client serve?",
    "options": [
      "To manage server-side logic",
      "To interact with the database",
      "To style user interfaces",
      "To handle API requests"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "To interact with the database"
  },
  {
    "no": "04",
    "question": "What is the purpose of Prisma Migrate?",
    "options": [
      "To handle HTTP requests",
      "To manage database schema changes",
      "To optimize frontend performance",
      "To create user interfaces"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "To manage database schema changes"
  },
  {
    "no": "05",
    "question": "Which database systems does Prisma support?",
    "options": [
      "MySQL and SQLite",
      "MongoDB and Cassandra",
      "PostgreSQL and MySQL",
      "Redis and Elasticsearch"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "PostgreSQL and MySQL"
  },
  {
    "no": "06",
    "question": "What is Prisma's schema defined in?",
    "options": [
      "JSON",
      "YAML",
      "GraphQL SDL (Schema Definition Language)",
      "XML"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "GraphQL SDL (Schema Definition Language)"
  },
  {
    "no": "07",
    "question": "What is the purpose of Prisma Client's query builder?",
    "options": [
      "To handle server-side caching",
      "To generate HTML templates",
      "To construct database queries",
      "To manage user authentication"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "To construct database queries"
  },
  {
    "no": "08",
    "question": "Which command is used to generate Prisma Client?",
    "options": [
      "prisma new",
      "prisma generate",
      "prisma create-client",
      "prisma init"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "prisma generate"
  },
  {
    "no": "09",
    "question": "What is the purpose of Prisma's 'introspection' feature?",
    "options": [
      "To analyze frontend code",
      "To generate API documentation",
      "To inspect the structure of a database",
      "To manage server logs"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "To inspect the structure of a database"
  },
  {
    "no": "10",
    "question": "What does Prisma's 'seeding' feature enable developers to do?",
    "options": [
      "To water their plants",
      "To optimize database performance",
      "To populate the database with initial data",
      "To generate automated tests"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "To populate the"
  }
]
